You put me in a box You told me to be sweet
The stardust girl, the perfect victim
You told me soften up You told me know your place
But you never saw the fire in my face Cause I'm not
your doll I'm not your pretty toy I'm not just a
picture for a poster boy I'm not your doll I'm
here to make a choice And I'm gonna make you hear
my voice
Rise!
You're scared of the noise You're scared of the
grit You're terrified that I'm not gonna fit In
the tiny world you built for me But I'm about to
set myself free Cause I'm not your doll I'm not
your pretty toy I'm not just a picture for a
poster boy I'm not your doll I'm here to make a
choice And I'm gonna make you hear
♪ Of my heart ♪
You are the story to be told Well, I'm the one
who'll break the mold You're what inside us, you
get the fire My voice is real and it's getting
higher
Cause I'm not your doll I'm not your pretty toy
I'm not just a picture for a poster boy I'm not
your doll I'm here to make a choice And I'm gonna
make you hear my voice
Not your doll
Hear my voice.